[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is Mias best friend in the 2001 Disney movie The Princess Diaries?", "correct_answer": "Lilly Moscovitz", "incorrect_answers": ["Lana", "Joe", "Michael Moscovitz"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Michael Curtizs movie, Casablanca, where were the visas to Portugal hidden ?", "correct_answer": "In Sams piano", "incorrect_answers": ["In Ricks file cabinet", "At the Airport", "In Ricks white dinner jacket"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In parts of Japan, if a black cat crosses your path, it means you will be very lucky.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Europe, the European Beaver (Castor fiber) was almost wiped out. It was driven to near extinction because of its fur and its scent gland that was used for medicinal purposes.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The dogfish is actually a common species of small shark.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which movie is the following tag line from:  Fear can hold you prisoner. Hope can set you free.", "correct_answer": "The Shawshank Redemption", "incorrect_answers": ["Bridge On The River Kwai", "Papillion", "Escape From Alcatraz"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Magnificent Seven Robert Vaughn played Harry Luck.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If 123facts.de existed, in which language would the quizzes most likely be written?", "correct_answer": "German", "incorrect_answers": ["French", "Danish", "Spanish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who voices Princess Fiona in Shrek 2?", "correct_answer": "Cameron Diaz", "incorrect_answers": ["Kirsten Dunst", "Katie Holmes", "Keira Knightley"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This old breed of cat has long fur. It originated in the Middle East, and some of its representatives have a flat face.", "correct_answer": "Persian", "incorrect_answers": ["Siamese", "Chinchilla", "Himalayan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Chocolate causes acne.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tony Shalhoub provided the voice of which of these characters from the animated film Cars?", "correct_answer": "Luigi", "incorrect_answers": ["Ramone", "Lightning McQueen", "Guido"]}]